{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Home Security Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40136/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40136,"taskName":"Alarm or Security System - Install","taskDescription":"Install an Alarm or Security System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Home Security Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":311,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Alarm Security System alarms protect","textMessagingName":"Install Alarm","rolloverLongDesc":"Companies in this category typically assess risk \u0026 budget \u0026 recommend \u0026 install specific devices to augment security. Note separate categories for cameras, guards, alarm monitoring \u0026 repairs.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes burglar, fire, smoke, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install an Alarm or Security System.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Home Security Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Home Alarm System","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":67,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Alarm System Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Alarm or Security System - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Security System Project","urlName":"Alarm-or-Security-System-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home Security Installation Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Alarm,Security,System,alarms,protect,surveillance,sercuirty,secure,safe,protection,burglar","emcCategoryOid":-12043,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":447,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40136/":{"taskOID":40136,"originalTaskOID":40136,"setID":447,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4009,"questionDisplayText":"Service Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of service do you need?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4134,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New Installation","answerDisplayText":"New Installation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":683,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition to an existing system","answerDisplayText":"Addition to an existing system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4010,"questionDisplayText":"Security Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the security features you would like to include in your system. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5536,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Securing doors","answerDisplayText":"Securing doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5538,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Securing windows","answerDisplayText":"Securing windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3968,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Motion detectors","answerDisplayText":"Motion detectors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2469,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fire/smoke protection","answerDisplayText":"Fire/smoke protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6691,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Video surveillance - not recorded","answerDisplayText":"Video surveillance - not recorded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6692,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Video surveillance - recorded","answerDisplayText":"Video surveillance - recorded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6693,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Video surveillance - remotely monitored","answerDisplayText":"Video surveillance - remotely monitored","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1310,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Central Monitoring","answerDisplayText":"Central Monitoring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7032,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Wireless System","answerDisplayText":"Wireless System","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4011,"questionDisplayText":"Keypad Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Enter the location where you would like a keypad.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3708,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Main entry","answerDisplayText":"Main entry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3770,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Master Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Master Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5583,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Service entry","answerDisplayText":"Service entry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4012,"questionDisplayText":"Wall Access","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Describe the wall access.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New construction or addition-all walls exposed","answerDisplayText":"New construction or addition-all walls exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5132,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel-all walls will be left exposed","answerDisplayText":"Remodel-all walls will be left exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5133,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remodel-partial wall access","answerDisplayText":"Remodel-partial wall access","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4123,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Neither-walls must be left intact","answerDisplayText":"Neither-walls must be left intact","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503453,"questionDisplayText":"If adding to an existing system, what is the brand of your current system?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"If adding to an existing system, what is the brand of your current system?","shortQuestionText":"If adding to an existing system, what is the brand of your current system?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":204472,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Not applicable","answerDisplayText":"Not applicable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204452,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"ADT","answerDisplayText":"ADT","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204453,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"DSC","answerDisplayText":"DSC","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204454,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Frontpoint","answerDisplayText":"Frontpoint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204455,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Honeywell","answerDisplayText":"Honeywell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204456,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"LiveWatch","answerDisplayText":"LiveWatch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204457,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Nest Secure","answerDisplayText":"Nest Secure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204458,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Protect America","answerDisplayText":"Protect America","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204459,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Ring","answerDisplayText":"Ring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204460,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Vivint","answerDisplayText":"Vivint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204461,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Unknown/Other","answerDisplayText":"Unknown/Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503454,"questionDisplayText":"If adding to an existing system, what is the age of your current system?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"If adding to an existing system, what is the age of your current system?","shortQuestionText":"If adding to an existing system, what is the age of your current system?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":204473,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Not applicable","answerDisplayText":"Not applicable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204462,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than a year","answerDisplayText":"Less than a year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204463,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1-5 years","answerDisplayText":"1-5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204464,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"5-10 years","answerDisplayText":"5-10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204465,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"10-15 years","answerDisplayText":"10-15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204466,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"15-20 years","answerDisplayText":"15-20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204467,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"20-25 years","answerDisplayText":"20-25 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204468,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"25+ years","answerDisplayText":"25+ years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4009,"questionDisplayText":"Service Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of service do you need?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4134,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New Installation","answerDisplayText":"New Installation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":683,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition to an existing system","answerDisplayText":"Addition to an existing system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4134,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New Installation","answerDisplayText":"New Installation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":683,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition to an existing system","answerDisplayText":"Addition to an existing system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4010,"questionDisplayText":"Security Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the security features you would like to include in your system. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5536,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Securing doors","answerDisplayText":"Securing doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5538,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Securing windows","answerDisplayText":"Securing windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3968,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Motion detectors","answerDisplayText":"Motion detectors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2469,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fire/smoke protection","answerDisplayText":"Fire/smoke protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6691,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Video surveillance - not recorded","answerDisplayText":"Video surveillance - not recorded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6692,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Video surveillance - recorded","answerDisplayText":"Video surveillance - recorded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6693,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Video surveillance - remotely monitored","answerDisplayText":"Video surveillance - remotely monitored","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1310,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Central Monitoring","answerDisplayText":"Central Monitoring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7032,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Wireless System","answerDisplayText":"Wireless System","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5536,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Securing doors","answerDisplayText":"Securing doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5538,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Securing windows","answerDisplayText":"Securing windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3968,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Motion detectors","answerDisplayText":"Motion detectors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2469,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fire/smoke protection","answerDisplayText":"Fire/smoke protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6691,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Video surveillance - not recorded","answerDisplayText":"Video surveillance - not recorded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6692,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Video surveillance - recorded","answerDisplayText":"Video surveillance - recorded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6693,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Video surveillance - remotely monitored","answerDisplayText":"Video surveillance - remotely monitored","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1310,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Central Monitoring","answerDisplayText":"Central Monitoring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7032,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Wireless System","answerDisplayText":"Wireless System","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4011,"questionDisplayText":"Keypad Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Enter the location where you would like a keypad.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3708,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Main entry","answerDisplayText":"Main entry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3770,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Master Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Master Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5583,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Service entry","answerDisplayText":"Service entry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3708,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Main entry","answerDisplayText":"Main entry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3770,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Master Bedroom","answerDisplayText":"Master Bedroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5583,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Service entry","answerDisplayText":"Service entry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4012,"questionDisplayText":"Wall Access","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Describe the wall access.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New construction or addition-all walls exposed","answerDisplayText":"New construction or addition-all walls exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5132,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel-all walls will be left exposed","answerDisplayText":"Remodel-all walls will be left exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5133,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remodel-partial wall access","answerDisplayText":"Remodel-partial wall access","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4123,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Neither-walls must be left intact","answerDisplayText":"Neither-walls must be left intact","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New construction or addition-all walls exposed","answerDisplayText":"New construction or addition-all walls exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5132,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remodel-all walls will be left exposed","answerDisplayText":"Remodel-all walls will be left exposed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5133,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remodel-partial wall access","answerDisplayText":"Remodel-partial wall access","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4123,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Neither-walls must be left intact","answerDisplayText":"Neither-walls must be left intact","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503453,"questionDisplayText":"If adding to an existing system, what is the brand of your current system?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"If adding to an existing system, what is the brand of your current system?","shortQuestionText":"If adding to an existing system, what is the brand of your current system?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":204472,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Not applicable","answerDisplayText":"Not applicable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204452,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"ADT","answerDisplayText":"ADT","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204453,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"DSC","answerDisplayText":"DSC","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204454,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Frontpoint","answerDisplayText":"Frontpoint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204455,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Honeywell","answerDisplayText":"Honeywell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204456,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"LiveWatch","answerDisplayText":"LiveWatch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204457,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Nest Secure","answerDisplayText":"Nest Secure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204458,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Protect America","answerDisplayText":"Protect America","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204459,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Ring","answerDisplayText":"Ring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204460,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Vivint","answerDisplayText":"Vivint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204461,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Unknown/Other","answerDisplayText":"Unknown/Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":204472,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Not applicable","answerDisplayText":"Not applicable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204452,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"ADT","answerDisplayText":"ADT","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204453,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"DSC","answerDisplayText":"DSC","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204454,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Frontpoint","answerDisplayText":"Frontpoint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204455,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Honeywell","answerDisplayText":"Honeywell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204456,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"LiveWatch","answerDisplayText":"LiveWatch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204457,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Nest Secure","answerDisplayText":"Nest Secure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204458,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Protect America","answerDisplayText":"Protect America","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204459,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Ring","answerDisplayText":"Ring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204460,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Vivint","answerDisplayText":"Vivint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204461,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Unknown/Other","answerDisplayText":"Unknown/Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503454,"questionDisplayText":"If adding to an existing system, what is the age of your current system?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"If adding to an existing system, what is the age of your current system?","shortQuestionText":"If adding to an existing system, what is the age of your current system?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":204473,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Not applicable","answerDisplayText":"Not applicable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204462,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than a year","answerDisplayText":"Less than a year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204463,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1-5 years","answerDisplayText":"1-5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204464,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"5-10 years","answerDisplayText":"5-10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204465,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"10-15 years","answerDisplayText":"10-15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204466,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"15-20 years","answerDisplayText":"15-20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204467,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"20-25 years","answerDisplayText":"20-25 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204468,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"25+ years","answerDisplayText":"25+ years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":204473,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Not applicable","answerDisplayText":"Not applicable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204462,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than a year","answerDisplayText":"Less than a year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204463,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1-5 years","answerDisplayText":"1-5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204464,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"5-10 years","answerDisplayText":"5-10 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204465,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"10-15 years","answerDisplayText":"10-15 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204466,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"15-20 years","answerDisplayText":"15-20 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204467,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"20-25 years","answerDisplayText":"20-25 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204468,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"25+ years","answerDisplayText":"25+ years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}